I'm not in.
Capro's in 21st place.
Twenty-fifth.
That's close.
more for you!
Hello everyone we are Niyazi Karljoy. This is Niyazijoy's second sushi project.
We are again visiting Karaj-san, but this time the members have changed from last time, Ayumi, Nico, and Yuka-chan are here.
We are visiting the chief neighbor next to Karaj-san.
This is the second time for Mitsuki to perform on the regular stage, so we will do our best.
This time we will be performing at Kurozushi, and we will be playing a popular Kurozushi menu item, "Black Jack 21".
Do you know Blackjack?
It's a card game where you have to get 21 cards in a row.
If you are in a team of two and the menu item you ordered is within the top 30 most popular menus at Kurozushi, you will receive a score according to your ranking.
If the menu is below 30th place, you get 0 points per rate.
If the total number of points for the menu items ordered by your team is exactly 21, you have cleared the competition.
The time limit is 45 minutes, and the team that guesses 21 first wins.
You have to order two or three items from the menu at a time, and there may be some side dishes, but this time you will only order sushi.
If you can't finish your meal, you will be disqualified.
So, let's eat as much as you can.
By the way, they have prepared some hints for us this time.
Thank you very much.
Eat the dessert.
2.Turn around and look at me.
3.Ask prettily.
Oh!
It's a little sweet.
So cute!
That's what you said.
Sounds like it's going to be difficult.
Let's do our best.
The final team will be Ayumi Yuuka-chan's team, Riko's team and my team.
I see...a team.
We are the same age.
Rigurashi-chan is there.
The team with the hair tied up, right?
Yes, we are.
Let's choose the team now.
Next time.
Let's ask for
One of my favorite.
Aburi cheese is delicious, isn't it?
I'll take you to the delicious Aburi Cheese Sandwich.
How many do you want?
How much do you think?
I don't think there's one in there.
I don't think it's in there.
Yes, it's okay.
Baked.
Yay!
Here you go.
Hamachi and...
Abujisalmon.
How many of each? How many?
The yellowtail...
Eighth, I think.
I think they're in the top 20.
The yellowtail in 21st place is...
Fourteenth?
Thirteen!
I think it's 13th.
Thirteenth, I think.
Okay, here we go. The teams with entries are red clams and scallion tuna.
Akagai is 10th, and I'm 11th.
I see. And I'm going in.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Delicious! Don't forget to eat!
Delicious.
Now then, let's hear the results of the competition.
Mr. Mitsubishi would like to announce the results.
Green onion tuna is No. 4.
That's high!
Fourth place is so high!
If it's No. 4...
Nagasaki is
Third.
Oh, you're number 30?
Then 4th.
Four points.
So you're popular.
Yeah, it's very popular.
It's going to be delicious.
Nagasaki would love to be number 30.
I'm so happy.
If Miki keeps eating red clams from now on...
Mr. Mitsubishi means...
Hamachi is
Second place.
Really?
Expensive? Hamachi?
We all love yellowtail.
Everybody loves hamachi.
Seared Cheese Salmon
Fifth place.
Oh, my God, that's high.
Seven points.
Seven.
It's winning.We're winning.
But just a little.
Banana's almost 21.
That's right.
But again, not even close.
Wait a minute. I'm surprised.
That's pretty high.
I was surprised to see Hamachi in second place.
Surprised.
Let's take this result into consideration for the next round.
Let's do our best!
The Nekomizuki team consisted of salmon, tsukkamaki, and shrimp.
Salmon was 3rd place, ttekkamaki was 8th place
and this shrimp is in 10th place
Our maika yuzu salt was predicted to be 10th place!
We ordered Tamachi Omejimi and it was #2, so we added it to the list and I think it was #11!
We ordered the YARI-IKA!
Squid to match!
Try squid!
I'm going to be squid!
Bon appétit!
Let's get the meat.
My stomach's still in knots.
Yes.
I'm doing this like a baked salmon, but I'm on my own.
LOL.
Thank you for the food.
It'll be gone soon.
By the way, Akira, how many plates do you usually eat?
Oh, that's right.
Oh, only a little.
Oh, that much?
It's not much.
How many people eat a lot?
Oh, yeah, like, 10 plates.
Not too many? How about you, Yuka?
I also eat about 10 plates.
I have 29 plates.
I'm going to have 30 plates?
I want to do better than that this time.
I don't have any more.
I haven't won anything in a long time.
I'll make an announcement.
Yuka and Neko's team...
Eight servings of salmon.
What? Isn't that low?
Sometimes, eight servings of Hi-Chew.
But we're still good.
Shrimp. I'm sorry.
17 plates.
25?
Oh, that's too bad.
I'm gonna have to cut my hand off.
I've got three plates full.
Miyata-san's entertaining.
Oh, my God!
He's only waiting in the middle of the last round.
No way!
Why did I order all of them?
What?
So you think we're like second place?
Not yet.
Let's go for it.
Let's go to the third round.
Let's go to the last round.
How much do I owe you?
I think Nentes Schullin's got a dime in it.
That's right.
You're buying grains, aren't you?
I'm buying grains.
Definitely buy the shrimp.
Fresh shrimp.
I like the salted adult ones better.
I think he likes it better than Nentesco.
Ice rolls are popular.
Let's see what they like.
Little kids love it.
The shrimp looks good.
Eat shrimp!
I can eat fried shrimp
I felt like a kid and asked for corn
I think little kids will eat it
Ranpai, which is not three-half full
No, no, no!
Costa bad!
Here is the team for marriage!
I chose the one-handed nigiri, the corn and the tutu tutu.
What's the number?
Curtains.
Three stores would make us 21, right? That's how we chose.
Okay, next question, please.
We are
Extreme aged tuna
Fortunate Big Eel
Seared shrimp cheese
I hope we can get close soon.
This looks good, doesn't it?
We could do it too, couldn't we?We can do it, can't we?
We're not? They're buzzing.
Let's get some bees.
I think we're gonna get the tut-tut.
Chewtraws.
Try it.
How does it feel?
Let's try it.
Let's eat it together.
What's it like?
The kandashi sauce, the fish, the soy sauce, it all melts in your mouth.
And the chutoro, the moment you put it in, it just melts in your mouth.
It's like dancing.
Eight minutes, please.
The one-handed nigiri isn't in.
Wait! This could be bad!
Wait a minute.
We're having a surprise dinner today.
He's here for dinner.
Looks like it's in there.
Corn on the cob is number 19.
What? He's in.
Wait a minute... what was I saying?
What? I'm looking at it.
Second place, second place, second place.
Second place.
No. 2.
I made a mistake.
Chutro is in 14th place.
Fourteenth?
No way!
Yuuka-san and Ayumi-san are in first place.
Yes.
Yuka-san, first place.
Yes, sir.
There are not many avikinis in the city
Urban legend Old
Heavy Mobilization of Violent Trails
Shredder
Tazawa
I did a video
Hanato
I'm going to the fourth round next.
I'd like to use a hint chance here.
Ayumi and Yuka-chan's team will use the number 1 dessert chance.
Riko Mitsuki's team will use the No. 2 "That way, that way, hoi chance.
Yes, sir.
The cute one is the last chapter
Cute is the first
Yes, so here is the sweets challenge
Dessert Chance
Not at all
Pint Chance
Pint Chance's dessert, you know, I eat pineapple.
You eat it with chopsticks.
Hmm? Delicious!
Yay!
mice
nora
ni
el
Apollo.
First of all, what did you say? I want to know what you said.
I need to know what you said.
What?
Wasn't it the egg or the octopus?
Yeah, so, are you asking me if it was an egg or an octopus? I mean...
Eggs or octopus.
You want to ask about the octopus because it looks like there's one in there?
You want me to ask?
Shall I ask him?
It's kind of comforting, isn't it?
That was cute.
I'll take a 10 on the octopus, please.
Not yet. Not yet.
Oh, you ate it? Octopus.
First, goo, then rock-paper-scissors.
I'll get the, uh...
No, no, no, no.
I was like, "Goo, rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
I've never done that before.
I have.
Good luck with that.
Are you okay?
I'm definitely not phobic.
Turn around and look at me. Here, ahh...
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's totally okay.
Until you lose.
I'm not losing.
First, goo, then rock, paper, scissors.
Turn around, hoi, ahhhh...
First goo, then rock, paper, scissors.
Turn around and face me.
I got your eye, I got your eye.
There was an eye.
So Vicomicky doesn't stand a chance?
No chance.
Come on, pretty please, try it.Pretty please, try it.
You want to do it with me?
I might do it with you.
Oh, yeah.
What do you say?
Okay, well, I'll leave you two to it.
Okay.
Can you give us a hint?
Cute, cute, cute.
Are you okay?
You're cute.
I want you to do a mosaic.
Here. Mosaic your voice, too.
Like, which product do you want to predict?
Uh, I don't know.
Eyelid wears, please.
It's not in there.
I just found out it's not in there.
I was just about to ask.
You're right, you're right, you're right, you're right.
I think it's in there.
I wonder if it's in there.
I'll take a closer look.
Nice center.
Please, please, please, please.
I want you to buy it.
Menu.
Something like Minty's.
They have it.
It's not here.
It's not in here.
It's like a minty.
That's for sure.
The Merikomiski team...
Salmon roe, eggs, and hand-rolled shrimp.
We have
Salmon roe, shrimp avocado and
Seared silver mackerel with yuzu salt.
Yes, sir!
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hm.
I don't know if 9th and 11th place is such a big deal.
I don't know.
I wonder what 21st place is.
Okay, here's the plan.
Okay.
First things first.
Okay, first things first.
Okay.
Demacky prawns.
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God.
The eggs are sweet.
Oh!
Not even two pieces of salmon roe.
What? No salmon roe?
One piece of salmon roe is 10.
One kan?
There's such a difference between 1 kan and 2 kan.
Why do they all have 2 pcs.
So, there is no salmon roe in the mom Emi's chain!
Aburi bottle soy sauce
It's not in there.
It's not in there!
Shrimp avocado
Looks like it's in there.
Maybe 30.
But I think everybody might have put it in there.
There's so many of them.
Not even close.
What are you eating?
I think if you ask for something you like, you'll get it.
We're running out of time.
This is the best.
Here you go.
I don't know what I ordered anymore.
Ten.
Nine, right?
It's done.
Is that a mussel?
What's in it?
I don't want any mussels.
Oh, like, not yet.
I'm not ready yet!
Looks so good!
Yes, sir!
The Mekomi Chicken Team
Mussels and...
Horse mackerel.
Horse mackerel and horse mackerel, with yellowfin tuna.
Yes!
Yes, sir!
The nice side is...
Kanden
I think it's 21.
Yes, sir! Last Chance for a Last Chance
We are
Tuna Grill andTuna Grill and
Kiwami Aged Cutting Board and
Matako
The order is "KANKEN" and "KANKEN
at the top
It's done!
Bon appétit!
I'll see you on the roster.
See you soon!
See you later!
Just a little too much
Just about full.
Still good?
Still got it.
That's great.
I can do it.
Are you sure?
You're pushing yourself.
You're pushing it.
I'll do it.
Yes, please.
Okay, bye.
High grain.
Thirteenth.
Oh, wow.
You're on the right track.
The merge is...
Oh, my God.
Good, good, good.
But we're still there.
We're stuck. We're stuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Eighth place, third place.
Boo-boo!
ana
Aaaaah!
40 points.
You want to be the team that regrets.
Let's see if we can make it.
Ten and 11.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
YUKE Tuna
Twelve.
Oh, you're here.
And 9.
It's still in there.
what is it?
Fifteenth.
Ahhh...
9th place would be awesome!
By the way
9th place is
Beef Ribs with Umadare
Oh!
I see.
You didn't say "meat sushi"?
It's true that little kids...
They eat meat, don't they?
Black salmon came in third.
I was number 21.
Third place.
You said kitchen.
Shrimp Wasa Dunk.
So the result is.
It's a tie, as neither of us could guess.
What a shame.
That was so close!
Thank you for the food!
I had to take a picture of you going home because I kuragued you this time, too.
Thank you very much.
Please look forward to the next video.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a good button too.
Bye bye!
[Please subscribe to our channel.